https://www.barouke.com/privacy.php

HOME | BLOG | FACEBOOK | TWITTER
MY ACCOUNT  |  SHOPPING CART  |  CHECKOUT
SHOP BY CATEGORIES
Wooden Bowls, Vases, Ikebana VesselsKaleidoscopesMirrorsClocks and Weather StationsWood Christmas OrnamentsLampsMarquetryWooden BoxesWooden JewelryWatches - HandmadeWooden FlowersKitchenMiscellaneous GiftsPewter, Copper, Silver, LeatherGamesMusical InstrumentsWind Chimes, Gongs, Wind BellsWooden Puzzles, BoxesInterlocking Jigsaw PuzzleOffice GiftsAccent Tables in Fine WoodsAccent Furniture
Video Gallery
View All Gallery Items
SHOP BY ARTIST
Please SelectBradford ChaucerCharles ElkanChesnik ScopesChristian BurchardCindy DrozdaCraig LossingD. MeierDan KvitkaDavid SengelDavid YeattsDavin and KeslerDennis BelcherEarl KennedyEduardo MilierisHeartwood CreationsHenry BergesonHilliard BoothHudson River InlayKovecsesLanny LyellLeonie LacouetteLloyd SumnerMike MikutowskiPat RobertsPeter ChapmanRichard CarnerRobert Rickard | Rickard StudioSpencer PetermanThe Tin Woodsman Pewter CompanyTom and Carol ParettiWarren Vienneau
SHOP BY PRICE
Under: $50
From:  $50 to $100
From:  $100 to $250
From:  $250 to $500
From:  $500 and above
SPECIAL OFFERS   »
Folding Rosewood Trivet$24.50$19.95
View All Special Offers
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting Barouke. Our privacy policy stipulates how we use personal information collected from you. You are encouraged to review this information upon each
visit to this site to ensure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
Note: The privacy practices set forth in this policy are for Barouke only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
Collection of Information: Barouke collects personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example, to add you to our mailing list.
Cookie Tracking :
Cookies are useful for gathering information such as tracking the number of visitors to Barouke, and understanding how our visitors use our site, in this way we will be able to improve upon the services that we offer you. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies. However, if you have previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.
Distribution of Information:
Any information submitted by you will be kept private. We do not sell and will never sell or barter your information to a third party.
Contact Information: If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:
Website:  www.barouke.com
Email: sales@barouke.com,
Phone: 910-762-4999
CART CONTENTS   »
0 items
REVIEWS     »
I love the new concept of the round cutting board. This is r ..
QUICK SEARCH
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Featured
Unique Accent Table with Maple Burl Top$695.00
INFORMATION
Visit Our BlogVisit Us On FaceBook
View All CategoriesView All Gallery ItemsView All VideosAbout BaroukeShipping & ReturnsSite MapPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseContact UsLinks of Interest
Home | About | Gallery | All Products | Special Offers | Shopping Cart | Contact Us | Shipping | Privacy Notice | Site MapCopyright © 2000 Barouke, Himax, Inc.
